question_data = [{"category": "Science: Computers",
                  "type": "boolean",
                  "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The first computer bug was formed by faulty wires.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.", "correct_answer": "True",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The average woman is 5 inches \/ 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                                      "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "In &quot;Overwatch,&quot; an allied McCree will say &quot;Step right up&quot; upon using his ultimate ability Deadeye.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                                      "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "In &quot;Team Fortress 2&quot;, the &quot;Bill&#039;s Hat&quot; is a reference to the game &quot;Dota 2&quot;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "There exists an island named &quot;Java&quot;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "&quot;The Division Bell&quot; is the final album of the progressive rock band Pink Floyd.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "E = MC3", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                                      "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                      "question": "The scientific name for the Southern Lights is Aurora Australis?",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
